mazumamobile.com 2014-05-19

# Phone Recycling, Recycle Mobile - Mazuma Mobile

## Who we are

In this privacy policy references to "we", "us" and "our" are to Mazuma Mobile. References to "our Website" or "the Website" are to www.mazumamobile.com.

## Other Websites

This privacy policy only covers this website. Any other websites which may be linked to by our website are subject to their own policy, which may differ from ours.

## What information we collect and how

The information we collect via the Website may include.

**1.** Any personal details you knowingly provide us with through forms and our email, such as name, address, telephone number etc.

**2.** In order to effectively process credit or debit card transactions it may be necessary for the bank or card processing agency to verify your personal details for authorisation outside the European Economic Area (EEA). Such information will not be transferred out of the EEA for any other purpose.

**3.** Your preferences and use of email updates, recorded by emails we send you (if you select to receive email updates on products and offers).

**4.** Your IP Address, this is a string of numbers unique to your computer that is recorded by our web server when you request any page or component on the Website. This information is used to monitor your usage of the Website.

**5.** Data recorded by the Website which allows us to recognise you and your preferred settings, this saves you from re-entering information on return visits to the site. Such data is recorded locally on your computer through the use of cookies. Most browsers can be programmed to reject, or warn you before downloading cookies, information regarding this may be found in your browsers 'help' facility.

## What we do with your information

Any personal information we collect from this website will be used in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998 and other applicable laws. The details we collect will be used:

**1.** To process your order, to provide after sales service.

**2.** In certain cases we may use your mail address to send you information on our other products and services. In such a case you will be offered the option to opt in/out before completing your purchase.

We may need to pass the information we collect to other companies for administrative purposes. We may use third parties to carry out certain activities, such as processing and sorting data, monitoring how customers use the Website, measuring customer service or issuing our e-mails for us. Third parties will not be allowed to use your personal information for their own purposes.

## Cookies

In order to sell your handset or device on the Mazuma Mobile website, your computer will need to accept cookies which are necessary for keeping track of what you have added to your Sales Basket, and whether or not you're logged in.

Our cookies do not store any personal information.

In addition to essential cookies, our website uses: 

  * 'performance' cookies which help us to see how the website is being used, and how we can improve the website in the future
  * 'functional' cookies which enable social media sharing and functionality

If you want to block or delete cookies from our website, you can do this via your web browsers privacy settings, however **you may find that certain areas of the website may not work properly**.
